I'm so confident.
我就是这么有信心
Because every woman
因为每个女人
Will love a man who can protect you.
会爱上一个可以保护你的男人。
What if I don't need your protection?
如果我不需要你的保护怎么办？
So I might be disappointed.
所以我可能会失望。
Perhaps he was so disappointed that he gave the letter to Luo Guanqun.
也许是太失望了，他把信交给了罗冠群。
Or Zhao An
还是赵安
What you are doing is not called protection.
你所做的不叫保护。
But it's intimidating.
但这很吓人。
Only a temporary threat
只是暂时的威胁
Waiting for you to really love me
等你真正爱我
will find that
会发现
That you want a threat from me
你想要我的威胁
nevermind
没关系
I know
我知道
You need time to accept all of this.
你需要时间来接受这一切。
but
但
We have plenty of time.
我们有充足的时间。
Use Chinese
使用中文
How to scold?
怎么骂？
rubbish
垃圾
You fool
你个笨蛋
This is an important list.
这是一个重要的清单。
Still got stolen
还是被盗了
Now why are you writing this?
现在你为什么要写这个？
What's the benefit?
有什么好处？
I'm incompetent.
我无能。
I hope the president
我希望总统
It will give me another chance to do good and make amends for my mistakes.
这将给我另一次做好事和弥补错误的机会。
chance
机会
You will also be known for doing bad deeds and doing good deeds.
你也会因做坏事和做好事而闻名。
Donation paper you need
您需要的捐款纸
Today I sprayed perfume.
今天我喷了香水。
cologne
科隆
I'm really very old.
我真的已经很老了。
Cologne and perfume
古龙水和香水
I can't tell the difference, can I?
我无法区分，可以吗？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Let's go.
我们走吧。
The manager is afraid.
经理害怕了。
Is Mr. Luo also there?
罗先生也在吗？
Master Chief
士官长
A guest you don't often see?
不常见到的客人？
You are a person who understands fashion.
你是一个懂时尚的人。
You try smelling it.
你尝试闻一下。
The perfume in my room is cologne.
我房间里的香水是古龙水。
Or perfume?
还是香水？
How can I understand?
我怎么能理解呢？
You have to ask Mr. Luo about this.
这个你得去问罗先生。
I don't understand what you guys are talking about.
我不明白你们在说什么。
I'll go first.
我先走了。
Master Chief
士官长
Is there anything I can help with?
有什么我可以帮忙的吗？
Lieutenant Chen
陈中尉
Two people stabbed
两人被刺伤
What business do you have when you come to me?
你来找我有什么事吗？
Boss Zhao invites you to eat at Hua You Hall.
赵老板请你去华友堂吃饭。
Master Chief
士官长
Master Lord's good wishes have been received.
领主大人的美好祝愿已经得到了。
But I'm busy.
但我很忙。
If not
如果不
Is Manager Luo also coming?
洛经理也来吗？
Let me tell you
让我告诉你
Make you have to go
让你不得不走
Why do you have to go eat?
为什么一定要去吃饭？
You'll know when you go.
你去的时候就知道了。
Khun Jua, outside, there are people looking for you.
Khun Jua，外面有人在找你。
Who came to me?
谁来找我？
I am Mr. Chen's colleague.
我是陈先生的同事。
What is the name of the great cavalry?
伟大的骑兵叫什么名字？
big spoon
大勺子
Mr. Jua
先生。知道
The Chen family had me pick you up to eat at Hua You Building.
陈家让我接你去华友大厦吃饭。
Why is there a problem with eating?
为什么吃饭会出现问题？
I don't know about this.
我不知道这个。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Guo Guo
Guo Guo
Why are you here?
你为什么在这？
Well, you gave it to me, didn't you?
好吧，你把它给了我，不是吗？
I didn't give it to you.
我没有给你。
enough
足够的
When it came
当它来的时候
There's no need to say that much.
没必要说那么多。
Then sit down carefully.
然后小心翼翼地坐下。
drink alcohol, eat food
喝酒、吃食物
invite
邀请
Please come.
请过来。
Come this way.
这边过来。
arrived
到达的
People have come and gone.
人们来了又走了。
This way.
这边走。
This is a family reunion.
这是一次家庭聚会。
Master Chief
士官长
It's waiting for the two of us.
它正在等待我们两个人。
Waiting for the two of you.
等待着你们两个。
Come on.
快点。
I'm sorry, everyone.
对不起，大家。
Come slowly.
慢慢来。
Come on.
快点。
You can sit down.
你可以坐下来。
sit there
坐在那里
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I'm sorry, everyone.
对不起，大家。
Then
然后
Let's eat and drink.
我们吃吃喝喝吧。
I'm still sitting here
我还坐在这里
This boss
这位老板
Please say something.
请说句话。
Everyone
每个人
Today, Zhao An had prepared cold liquor.
今天，赵安准备了凉酒。
The main thing is during this period of work.
最主要的是这段时间的工作。
in the work of our company
在我们公司的工作中
Harassing Mr. Zuo and Boss Chen
骚扰左先生和陈老板
For this
为了这
It is an apology to both of you.
这是对你们俩的道歉。
Don't.
不。
Master Chief
士官长
It's all for work.
一切都是为了工作。
Don't take it to heart.
别放在心上。
I also have to pay attention.
我也得注意。
Khun Noo Chua
蔡坤诺
I adjusted one glass of liquor.
我调了一杯酒。
good
好的
Master Chief is a high society person, right?
士官长是上流社会人士吧？
That is,
那是，
Anyway, we can adjust our understanding.
不管怎样，我们可以调整一下我们的认识。
It's the same family.
这是同一个家庭。
Don't care.
别在意。
-Hurry up and eat this.-Okay.
-快点吃这个。-好的。
This is just my first glass.
这只是我的第一杯。
Everyone was waiting for the second cup of wine.
大家都在等待第二杯酒。
Sit.
坐。
Punishment for the second cup of liquor
第二杯酒的惩罚
I must punish the two of you.
我必须惩罚你们两个。
we
我们
You two
你们俩
Every day is intimate and loving.
每一天都是亲密而充满爱的。
Strong and passionate
坚强而热情
It's because everyone is jealous.
就是因为大家都嫉妒。
Will you be punished?
你会受到惩罚吗？
punish
惩治
Good, punish me.
好啊，惩罚我吧。
So take it like this.
所以就这样吧。
I don't have a stiff neck.
我没有脖子僵硬。
You're tougher than me.
你比我还坚强。
I replace you
我代替你
okay
好的
Protect like this
这样保护
That's it.
就是这样。
very good
非常好
This third cup of liquor was the liquor that everyone had been waiting for the most.
这第三杯酒，是大家最期待的酒。
Auspicious liquor for both of you
祝你们俩的吉祥酒
Master Chief
士官长
heart
心
kindness
善良
I have received kindness.
我得到了善意。
but
但
It's like this.
就像这样。
Me and Guo Guo
Me and Guo Guo
Before, the two of us
之前我们两个人
We've talked about this.
我们已经讨论过这个了。
At this time, there are no plans to get married.
目前，还没有结婚的计划。
Let's talk in another two years.
再过两年再聊吧。
Marriage deepens feelings.
婚姻加深了感情。
Your feelings are already this deep.
你们的感情已经这么深了。
Water flows in and the wind accelerates.
水流进来，风加速。
Right?
正确的？
Everyone poured liquor.
大家都倒了酒。
Don't.
不。
this
这
This is just a big deal.
这只是一件大事。
Master Chief
士官长
Boss Chen
陈老板
Are you still angry at me?
你还在生我的气吗？
You told me honestly.
你诚实地告诉我。
The very first episode
第一集
I've always wondered about your relationship.
我一直很好奇你们的关系。
fake couple
假情侣
But now
但现在
They were the ones who told me that it was fake.
是他们告诉我这是假的。
I do not believe
我不相信
Will everyone believe it?
大家会相信吗？
do not believe
不相信
Master Chief
士官长
You haven't asked me yet.
你还没问过我。
I thought we were married now.
我以为我们现在已经结婚了。
feeling too worried
感到太担心
yes
是的
Guo Guo is still not ready to marry me.
果果还没准备好嫁给我。
Shuang Tao is a woman.
Shuang Tao is a woman.
It is said that women should preserve their bodies.
都说女人要保养自己的身体。
If he doesn't want to marry you
如果他不想跟你结婚
Why did you have to come all the way to Shanghai?
你为什么要千里迢迢来到上海？
Is that right?
是对的吗？
Shuangtao
Shuangtao
I understand you
我理解你
Do you want to propose?
你想求婚吗？
You really don't understand me.
你真的不明白我。
You look at this shop.
你看看这家店。
If you want money, you can't.
如果你想要钱，你就不能。
There will be no work.
不会有工作。
It's very different from what I asked for.
这和我要求的有很大不同。
Now I can't marry him.
现在我不能嫁给他了。
Now this is the thing I regret the most later.
现在这是我后来最后悔的一件事。
is to welcome you to stay in Shanghai
是欢迎您入住上海
You look.
你看。
On this beach
在这个海滩上
There are only talented young men, right?
只有有才华的年轻人吧？
I'm under a lot of pressure.
我压力很大。
peaceful family
和睦的家庭
Create a stable family
建立稳定的家庭
One more thing
还有一件事
Who is your uncle-in-law?
你的舅舅是谁？
If you marry Mr. Jua
如果你嫁给Jua先生
Our Thai and commercial banks
我们的泰国银行和商业银行
It can be increased as well.
它也可以增加。
Next is the life of all of us.
接下来就是我们大家的生活了。
It will be loud like a firework.
声音会像烟花一样响亮。
Therefore, the matter of marriage
所以，婚姻这件事
You must dress
你必须穿好衣服
Come on.
快点。
Everyone come and propose to me.
大家都来向我求婚。
Marriage proposal
求婚
congratulations
恭喜
If you promise to marry into the Chen family
如果你答应嫁入陈家
I will reveal your secret
我会透露你的秘密
Congratulations.
恭喜。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
And how dare each of them?
他们每个人怎么敢？
Master Chief
士官长
Are you married?
你结婚了吗？
It seemed like it was between the two of them.
看起来就像是他们两个人之间的事。
If she agrees
如果她同意的话
This is a good thing.
这是一件好事。
But now I've seen it.
但现在我已经看到了。
Zuo Shuangxiu was not pleased.
Zuo Shuangxiu was not pleased.
You guys are strong.
你们很坚强。
I'm forcing people's hearts.
我是在逼迫人心。
That's it.
就是这样。
Men watch for many years and play for many years, don't they?
男人看很多年，玩很多年，不是吗？
Do you like this today?
今天你喜欢这个吗？
And tomorrow I'll like it again.
明天我会再次喜欢它。
Why do you have to let him get married so quickly?
为什么非得这么快让他结婚呢？
Hasn't that taken away your right to choose your work?
这不是剥夺了你选择工作的权利吗？
So what is most important?
那么什么是最重要的呢？
Parents' orders
父母的命令
Is that right?
是对的吗？
Request from the matchmaker
媒人请求
Even now I am searching for a new and peaceful life.
即使现在我也在寻找新的、平静的生活。
But big things like marriage
但婚姻这样的大事
Do both parents still have to agree?
还得双方父母都同意吗？
Is that right?
是对的吗？
Jiaping
Jiaping
normal
普通的
You call me your son.
你称我为你的儿子。
The ancients said
古人说
Big Brother is Father
大哥是父亲
In this matter, I will help you decide.
这件事情，我来帮你决定。
You're not just my brother.
你不仅仅是我的兄弟。
Do you want to be my father?
你想成为我的父亲吗？
But I don't agree.
但我不同意。
Don't you think of taking advantage of me.
你就别想利用我了。
I can go this way.
我可以走这条路。
The parents of young children are not discouraged at all.
年幼孩子的父母一点也不气馁。
Luo Guanqun's status
Luo Guanqun's status
You don't care
你不在乎
So, can I apply for the position?
那么，我可以申请这个职位吗？
President Kimura-san
社长 木村先生
Uncle-in-law
舅舅
My aunt called me.
我阿姨打电话给我。
that you come to Shanghai
说你来上海
But a few days ago
但前几天
Manage business matters in Suzhou
管理苏州的商务事宜
I don't have time to take care of you.
我没时间照顾你。
Please disturb the manager.
请打扰管理员。
Both of you were honored.
你们俩都很荣幸。
Please accept it.
请接受。
Sit down.
坐下。
Invite Mr. Kimura-san.
邀请木村先生。
Sit.
坐。
You are Chen Jiaping.
You are Chen Jiaping.
Khun Awee?
坤阿维？
No, Uncle.
不，叔叔。
you will come
你会来
Please tell me.
请告诉我。
I'll pick you up first.
我先去接你。
I don't see the need to be so considerate.
我不认为有必要如此体贴。
Today I went to see Governor Kimura.
今天我去见了木村知事。
Talk about your marriage.
谈谈你的婚姻。
It's a good thing.
这是一件好事。
So we came uninvited.
所以我们不请自来。
It's good.
很好。
Baan Ping
工作平
Look on your side, you have Chief Kimura.
看看你这边，有木村队长。
Mr. Zuo, on this side, there is Chief Yu.
左先生，这边是于科长。
Can this be compensated?
这个可以补偿吗？
yes
是的
It has Japanese and Japanese goodness.
它有日本和日本的优点。
East Asia prospers together.
东亚共同繁荣。
The situation is very good.
情况非常好。
The Chen family has outstanding abilities over the new government.
陈氏家族在新政府上有着出色的能力。
Zuo Shuang Tao
Zuo Shuang Tao
She is the granddaughter of our business owner Yu.
她是我们企业主于的孙女。
The combination of the two of you
你们两个的结合
It is an example of a new and peaceful life.
这是新的和平生活的一个例子。
yes
是的
It really means a lot.
这确实意义重大。
Zuo Shuang Tao
Zuo Shuang Tao
Chen surname
陈姓
If the two of you still don't agree.
如果你们两个还是不同意。
Isn't this turning into an anti-Heping movement?
这不是变成反和平运动吗？
Yes, yes.
是的是的。
Waiting for your wedding
等待你的婚礼
I will invite the person in charge of promoting peaceful life.
我会邀请促进和平生活的负责人。
Takeo Tazashiyamashima
田座山岛武夫
Give this wedding
给这场婚礼
Let it be an important ceremony of friendship between China and Japan.
让它成为中日友好的一个重要仪式。
good
好的
Let's drink together
我们一起喝吧
crash
碰撞
Crash.
碰撞。
Take it like this.
就这样吧。
Kimura-san
木村桑
Thank you for your promotion and support.
感谢您的推广和支持。
I want to drink just for you.
我想只为你喝一杯。
good
好的
And I am our Guo Guo representative.
我是我们果果代表。
You're not good at drinking.
你不擅长喝酒。
I'd like to drink another glass for you.
我想再为你喝一杯。
Uncle
叔叔
First time meeting
第一次见面
I'd like to drink this glass of wine for you.
我想为你喝这杯酒。
There's more.
还有更多。
The head of the Luo Lord
洛主头像
and everyone sitting here
和坐在这里的每个人
I'd like to drink to everyone.
我想给大家干一杯。
Take it like this.
就这样吧。
I finished this bottle of liquor, is that okay?
我把这瓶酒喝完了，可以吗？
This isn't necessary.
这是没有必要的。
Drink a little.
喝一点。
You don't waste time on work.
你不会把时间浪费在工作上。
flat house
平房
Jiaping
Jiaping
marry
结婚
But I think
但我觉得
They forced me to get married
他们强迫我结婚
It's not that easy.
它不是那么容易。
marry
结婚
So, what is Chen Jiaping's attitude?
那么，陈家平是什么态度呢？
He's drunk.
他喝醉了。
I don't know if I'm really drunk or pretending to be drunk.
我不知道自己是真醉还是假醉。
If it's like you said
如果真像你说的那样
Whether it is Kimura Kenzan Luo Kuangjun
Whether it is Kimura Kenzan Luo Kuangjun
Or even being considerate still pressures you.
或者甚至体贴仍然会给你带来压力。
This was probably not Zhao An's idea alone.
这恐怕不是赵安一个人的主意。
yes
是的
But in that situation
但在那种情况下
I just can't accept it.
我就是无法接受。
And there's no denying it.
无可否认。
All I could do was drink non-stop.
我能做的就是不停地喝。
Get yourself drunk
把自己灌醉
Find some extra time.
找一些额外的时间。
So what do you plan to do next?
那么接下来你打算做什么？
This is a good opportunity for us.
这对我们来说是一个很好的机会。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
If a mountain warrior comes to your wedding
如果山地战士来参加你的婚礼
We can carry out an assassination attempt.
我们可以进行一次暗杀行动。
and brought back the secret letter
并带回了那封密信
I can also go to the group for help.
我也可以去群里寻求帮助。
You can go ask for help from the Taochun Hurricane Team.
你可以去桃春飓风队寻求帮助。
so that we can be sure that
这样我们就可以确定
will be able to evacuate safely
将能够安全撤离
So what to do with the Chen family?
那么陈家该怎么办呢？
He will be questioned as an accomplice in the foothill murders.
他将作为山麓谋杀案的同谋接受讯问。
The Japanese will definitely not let him go.
日本人是绝对不会放过他的。
He is a traitor.
他是一个叛徒。
Don't you like traitors?
你不喜欢叛徒吗？
Why should you be worried about him?
你为什么要担心他？
I'm not.
我不是。
I just feel
我只是觉得
They suddenly forced us to get married, it was very strange.
他们突然强迫我们结婚，这很奇怪。
It felt like there was another goal.
感觉好像还有另一个目标。
So we use a combination of plans.
所以我们使用计划的组合。
What if the Chen family doesn't approve of the marriage?
万一陈家不同意这门亲事怎么办？
So you were forced to marry?
所以你是被迫结婚的？
Since Zhao Anluo was quantifying Mu Chun
Since Zhao Anluo was quantifying Mu Chun
And then there's also kindness.
然后还有善意。
Many people want to help with your wedding.
许多人想为您的婚礼提供帮助。
What are you afraid of?
你怕什么呢？
both soft and hard
软硬皆可
Force until he gives permission?
强迫直到他允许？
Boss Liu
刘老板
It must have been this difficult to assassinate at the foot of the mountain.
在山下刺杀肯定是这么困难。
What exactly is the goal?
目标到底是什么？
Haven't I already told you?
我不是已经告诉过你了吗？
In his hand he has a secret letter that we need.
他手里拿着一封我们需要的密信。
But I heard that
但我听说
A nobleman fights from the foot of a mountain with a soldier.
一位贵族与一名士兵在山下战斗。
secretly collude
暗中勾结
Smuggling drugs into the territory
走私毒品进入境内
Later, because the separation of the middle items was not equal
后来因为中间物品的分离不均等
So he wanted to reveal it to the news agency.
所以他想把这件事透露给新闻机构。
The name of this senior nobleman
这位高级贵族的名字
Taking back secret information is no small matter.
收回机密信息可不是小事。
It must have been this high-ranking nobleman to get the matter to matter.
一定是这位高级贵族让这件事闹大了。
Now the winged child has strong legs.
现在长翅膀的孩子有了强壮的腿。
Who sent you to investigate?
谁派你来调查的？
I am really disappointed for Xiao Hu and Da Xuan.
我真的对小胡和大轩很失望。
Our mission is mission success.
我们的使命是使命成功。
There's no need to ask too much about other things.
其他的事情没必要问太多。
yes
是的
Consider it that I took revenge on Xiao Hu and Da Xuan's behalf.
就当我替小虎和大轩报仇吧。
can
能
And then there's the kid who threatened you.
还有那个威胁你的孩子。
Take care of him as quickly as you can.
尽快照顾他。
Otherwise it will ruin our story.
否则就会毁了我们的故事。
If they really got married
如果他们真的结婚了
At the wedding ceremony, I had to assassinate the mountain chief.
婚礼上，我不得不刺杀山长。
Even if you can escape
就算你能逃脱
Chen Jiaping died at the same time.
陈家平同时去世。
who
WHO
I am Zuo Shuangtao
I am Zuo Shuangtao
Mr. Jua
先生。知道
How do you know I'm here?
你怎么知道我在这里？
You come out of the coffee shop.
你从咖啡店出来。
I've followed you.
我已经跟着你了。
Why
为什么
Don't you welcome me?
你不欢迎我吗？
No, no.
不，不。
Please come in.
请进来。
Come find me this late.
这么晚了来找我吧。
Is anything up?
有什么事吗？
The person you like keeps coming to you.
你喜欢的人总会来找你。
Ask like this
像这样问
Aren't you stupid?
你不是傻子吗？
no
不
Well, my house is a little messy.
嗯，我家有点乱。
Normally when you drink coffee
一般情况下喝咖啡的时候
yes
是的
Can you make me a glass?
你能给我一杯吗？
Absolutely no problem.
绝对没问题。
Are you alone?
你一个人吗？
yes
是的
When did you start liking me?
你什么时候开始喜欢我的？
Since seeing your picture
自从看到你的照片
Have you told others about the story you like about me?
你有没有告诉过别人你喜欢我的故事？
nothing
没有什么
I don't have many friends.
我没有很多朋友。
Water temperature 93 degrees
水温93度
It is the ideal temperature for making coffee.
这是冲泡咖啡的理想温度。
This kettle was boiled half an hour ago.
这壶半小时前就烧开了。
It's Baidu.
是百度。
The temperature is about 20 degrees.
气温在20度左右。
The speed at which hot water cools
热水冷却的速度
It is proportional to the temperature of the hot water in the air.
它与空气中热水的温度成正比。
Therefore, the temperature of the water in this kettle is just right.
所以，这个水壶里的水温刚刚好。
This is the latest we received from
这是我们收到的最新消息
in our shanghai
在我们上海
The identity of the news sender is unclear.
消息发送者的身份尚不清楚。
Come and invite.
快来邀请吧。
Sit there.
坐那儿。
If I marry into the Chen family
如果我嫁入陈家
Will you expose me?
你会揭发我吗？
I know why you came here.
我知道你为什么来这里。
There's no way I'm going to give you a letter.
我不可能给你写信。
Mom saw it just now.
妈妈刚才看到了。
In the closet you have a news machine.
壁橱里有一台新闻机。
It's garbage.
这是垃圾。
It's no use.
这是没有用的。
But you can fix it.
但你可以修复它。
Why are you asking these things?
你为什么问这些事情？
You don't just get the repair done.
您不只是完成维修。
You still use it to send telegrams.
您仍然用它来发送电报。
I don't understand what you are saying.
我不懂你在说什么。
You are the one who sent the secret telegram to the security station.
你就是给保安站发密电的人。
Right?
正确的？
I do not have
我没有
Your machine number 45 A 3 - 8
您的机器编号 45 A 3 - 8
seized from the bureaucracy
从官僚机构中夺取
From the special habits of newspaper carriers in the past
从过去报刊携带者的特殊习惯来看
Causes wear and tear on the electrical buttons.
导致电气按钮磨损。
Therefore, the person receiving the message can use these characteristics.
因此，接收消息的人可以利用这些特征。
To separate this message
分隔此消息
It's a message sent from number 45 A 3 - 8.
这是从号码 45 A 3 - 8 发送的消息。
Who exactly are you?
你到底是谁？
Why do you know these things?
你为什么知道这些事情？
You answered my question first.
你先回答了我的问题。
What if I'm not happy?
如果我不高兴怎么办？
I bet you don't like the consequences of not answering.
我打赌你不喜欢不回答的后果。
Okay.
好的。
I accept
我接受
That telegram was sent by me.
那封电报是我发出的。
But why do you have a telegram?
但你为什么有电报呢？
or that
或者那个
You are a soldier too.
你也是一名军人。
What kind of work do Chen Jiaping people do?
陈家坪人是做什么工作的？
Don't you know?
你不知道吗？
Military units have their people.
军事单位有他们的人。
So this secret message can be brought.
所以这个秘密消息是可以带来的。
Answer me
回答我
Why must you send a secret message to the commander?
为什么一定要给指挥官发密信？
I
我
I happened to meet
我碰巧遇见了
their station by chance
他们的车站偶然
So I want to try that.
所以我想尝试一下。
Will they be able to crack my code?
他们能破解我的密码吗？
I just want to play.
我只是想玩。
I believe
我相信
But do you think Zhao An and the Japanese will believe it?
但你觉得赵安和日本人会相信吗？
How do you take it?
你觉得怎么样？
exchange
交换
Give me the letter back.
把信还给我。
go back
回去
I give you a secret letter.
我给你一封秘密信。
Who exactly are you?
你到底是谁？
Why did the previous letter have to be forged?
为什么之前的信必须是伪造的？
We all have secrets from each other.
我们都有彼此的秘密。
Isn't this good?
这不是很好吗？
Zhao An and Luo Guanqun are suspicious of you.
赵安和罗冠群都怀疑你了。
You'd better hurry and leave.
你最好快点离开。
Are you really worried about me?
你真的担心我吗？
Whoever you are
无论你是谁
I hope you are safe.
我希望你安全。
I'll definitely leave.
我一定会离开。
But not now
但是不是现在
It's true.
这是真的。
Information in your secret message
您的秘密消息中的信息
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
It's true
这是真的
I accidentally heard from Zhao An.
无意中听到了赵安的消息。
Therefore, you hope to succeed in uniting the foothill assassin soldiers.
因此，你希望能成功联合山麓刺客士兵。
His hand was stained with Chinese blood.
他的手上沾满了中国人的鲜血。
He deserves to die.
他该死。
I have to go
我得走了
Thank you for your coffee.
谢谢你的咖啡。
at least
至少
Now I don't hate you that much.
现在我没那么恨你了。
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
Auntie-in-law
阿姨
good morning
早上好
Shuangtao
Shuangtao
My uncle-in-law
我的舅舅
told me all
告诉我一切
How good are the stories?
这些故事有多好？
Why didn't you tell me immediately?
你为什么不立即告诉我？
When are you preparing to organize it?
你准备什么时候组织？
He hasn't asked to marry me yet.
他还没有向我求婚。
One more thing
还有一件事
I want to see this person.
我想见见这个人。
Will he be sincere or not?
他到底是真心还是假意？
yes
是的
You shouldn't say yes easily.
你不应该轻易说“是”。
Don't let it get any cheaper than this kid.
别让它比这孩子便宜。
After all, you are the elder young lady of the Yu family.
毕竟你是于家的大小姐啊。
Right?
正确的？
Of course.
当然。
Mr. Jua
先生。知道
your phone
您的手机
Let's go.
我们走吧。
hello
你好
Mr. Jua
先生。知道
I am Xiu Cai
我是秀才
Boss Chen drank too much last night.
陈老板昨晚喝多了。
Tonight, I got up to go to the bathroom and accidentally fell.
今晚，我起身去卫生间，不小心摔倒了。
Now lying in the hospital
现在躺在医院里
Are you seriously injured?
你伤得很重吗？
It's a little affected.
是有点影响了。
But the doctor said it would be better if I slept for 2 days.
但医生说睡2天会好一些。
Boss Chen asked you to tell me.
陈老板让你告诉我。
I know, thank you.
我知道了，谢谢。
Falling until your head breaks
跌倒直到你的头摔断
It's nothing serious.
没什么严重的。
Rest for a few days and it will go away.
休息几天就会消失。
But the patient's face was hit very hard.
但病人的脸受到了很大的打击。
Said I don't want you to see
说我不想让你看到
Ugly appearance
相貌丑陋
I refuse to see you.
我拒绝见你。
So, please help me give him this.
所以，请帮我把这个交给他。
good
好的
with the gate
与门
During this time I go to the hospital every day.
这段时间我每天都去医院。
Deliver food to the Chen family
给陈家送饭
But the person named Chen Jiaping
但那个叫陈家平的人
refuse to show up
拒绝出现
So what do you think this Chen Jiaping means?
那么你觉得这个陈家平是什么意思呢？
Fear before marriage
婚前恐惧
Already in this situation
已经是这种情况了
If he doesn't escape
如果他不逃的话
Don't escape
不要逃跑
He will not flee or flee.
他不会逃跑，也不会逃跑。
What do you think he's waiting for?
你觉得他在等什么？
wait
等待
No matter what
无论
Anyway, today he had to leave the hospital.
无论如何，今天他必须出院了。
I said
我说
He had nowhere else to hide.
他无处可藏。
I don't know when he went.
我不知道他什么时候走的。
Today I went out early in the morning.
今天我一早就出去了。
thank you
谢谢
Mr. Jua
先生。知道
Today, Chief Chen ordered:
今天，陈局长下令：
That won't let you go up
那不会让你上升
he
他
Mr. Jua
先生。知道
Chen surname
陈姓
open the door
打开门
Why are you avoiding me?
你为什么躲着我？
Is there anything that can't be said face to face?
有什么不能当面说的吗？
open the door
打开门
Mr. Jua
先生。知道
Boss Chen looks like he's on the 4th floor.
陈老板看起来是在四楼。
What about the Chen family?
陈家呢？
How was I supposed to know?
我怎么知道？
After all, you have to drink auspicious liquor, right?
毕竟吉祥酒总得喝吧？
Why can't I find myself?
为什么我找不到自己？
Chen surname
陈姓
You come out now.
你现在就出来吧。
Chen Jiaping
Chen Jiaping
I know you're inside
我知道你在里面
Why must you avoid me?
为什么你一定要避开我？
Chen surname
陈姓
The Chen family, hurry up and come out.
陈家的人，赶紧出来吧。
Do you remember one year ago?
你还记得一年前吗？
We have an agreement that
我们有一个协议
We've agreed.
我们已经同意了。
will go together
会一起去
and travel together
并一起旅行
But you
但是你
Why didn't you come that day?
那天你怎么没来？
This time, if it weren't for the fact that there were many people matching us.
这一次，如果不是匹配我们的人很多。
I don't dare to talk about these things with you.
我不敢和你谈论这些事情。
Chen surname
陈姓
Now I can't wait.
现在我已经等不及了。
I want to ask you that
我想问你
What do you really think?
你到底怎么想？
Qian Xiucai
Qian Xiucai
Boss Chen
陈老板
Released and released from the hospital.
已出院并出院。
Have you been released from the hospital?
你已经出院了吗？
There's nothing else, right?
没有别的事了吧？
Everyone is worried about you.
每个人都担心你。
nevermind
没关系
Just a small wound.
只是一个小伤口。
yes
是的
Boss Chen
陈老板
today morning
今天早上
Someone brought a bag for me.
有人给我带来了一个袋子。
and said that inside it all belonged to you
并说里面的一切都属于你
yes
是的
Where is
哪里
I'll go get it for you.
我去给你拿一下。
Kimura-san
木村桑
Carrying out the plan too quickly
计划执行得太快
Boss Chen
陈老板
This big bag
这个大包
What's inside?
里面是什么？
You'll know for yourself.
你自己就会知道。
Okay.
好的。
thank you
谢谢
nevermind
没关系
according to your plan
根据你的计划
Waiting to find enough funds
等待找到足够的资金
What month and what year?
哪年哪月？
Kimura-san
木村桑
Our trade here is no less difficult.
我们在这里的贸易也同样困难。
After the Emperor's army began to attack slowly.
之后，帝军开始缓缓进攻。
Agriculture and Industry in Chongqing Government Occupied Areas
重庆政府驻区的农业和工业
Therefore gradually recovering
因此逐渐康复
There is a shortage of supplies, not as much as before.
物资短缺，不像以前那么严重了。
The area is not very different.
地区差别不大。
Ordinary materials such as Satuan and Praewa cloth are available here.
普通材料如 Satuan 和 Praewa 布都可以在这里买到。
Sell ​​it that way.
就这样卖吧。
The price couldn't be beat before.
以前的价格是无与伦比的。
drug
药品
If we compare the medicine with the things we bought
如果我们将药物与我们购买的东西进行比较
But what we have accumulated is limitless.
但我们所积累的却是无限的。
So this much money
这么多钱
When getting ready
准备时
This is quite
这相当
There are always more solutions than problems.
解决方案总是比问题多。
yes
是的
What is your opinion?
你有什么意见？
I think
我认为
How are you?
你好吗？
You've evolved.
你已经进化了。
Thank you for your compliment, Mr. Chairman.
谢谢主席先生的夸奖。
like this
像这样
Help solve urgent problems.
帮助解决紧急问题。
More importantly,
更重要的是，
You found another one.
你找到了另一个。
I cannot do
我不能做
If I don't know, I wouldn't dare.
如果我不知道，我就不敢。
If you don't dare, you won't.
如果你不敢，你就不会。
owner
所有者
The plan must be revised.
该计划必须修改。
It's true.
这是真的。
How are you preparing for the special meeting?
你为这次特别会议准备得怎么样了？
There are still some programs that need to go.
还有一些计划需要取消。
Almost finished
就快结束了
Tomorrow I will go to Nanjing.
明天我要去南京。
Come back in a week.
一周后回来。
Take your new plan.
采取你的新计划。
Go to a special meeting with me.
和我一起去参加一个特别会议。
yes
是的
Another thing is
另一件事是
must be kept secret
必须保密
In particular, there was still no finding of the four dok mei items.
尤其是，四件独美物品仍未找到。
Mr. Kimura, you can trust us.
木村先生，您可以相信我们。
Before the special meeting
特别会议之前
This plan will not be one step away from me.
这个计划不会离我一步之遥。
goodbye
再见
Do you remember one year ago?
你还记得一年前吗？
We had one promise together.
我们有一个共同的承诺。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
We have agreed.
我们已经同意了。
Are you watching a drama?
你在看话剧吗？
Let's hang out together.
我们一起出去玩吧。
But what about you?
但你呢？
The Chen family was inside.
陈家人就在里面。
It must be right.
一定是对的。
Why don't you open the door?
你为什么不开门？
That's a man.
那是一个男人。
When you're done eating, are you going to run away?
吃完饭你就跑吗？
Who has the key to the warehouse door?
谁有仓库门的钥匙？
The Chen family has
陈氏家族有
kick out
踢出
I don't see the need to do this at all.
我认为根本没有必要这样做。
I'm sorry, Guo Guo.
对不起，果果。
I
我
I've been avoiding you all week.
我整个星期都在躲着你。
Because I don't want to use
因为我不想用
Picture of a swollen face
脸肿的图片
I'm asking you to marry me.
我向你求婚。
But these past several days
但这几天
No matter the time, I miss you.
无论什么时候，我都想念你。
What I hate about myself is
我讨厌自己的一点是
No matter how I use
不管我怎么用
Or what kind of marriage proposal?
或者什么样的求婚？
It's not enough to show my love
不足以表达我的爱
Because in my heart
因为在我心里
You are the only person in the world
你是世界上唯一的人
So use a unique marriage proposal.
因此，请使用独特的求婚方式。
To be worthy of you
才配得上你
but
但
But I'm sorry.
但我很抱歉。
I really can't think of anything.
我实在想不出什么了。
I
我
I won't say words that make you shake.
我不会说让你动摇的话。
But I want to grow old with you.
但我想和你一起变老。
In fact, for many years now
事实上，多年来
There is one sentence.
有一句话。
in my mind
在我脑海里
in my dream
在我梦里
I've said it a thousand times.
我已经说过一千遍了。
But today
但今天
I finally had a chance to say it.
我终于有机会说出来了。
Guo Guo
Guo Guo
Please marry me.
请嫁给我。
Why did you say you didn't want to see me?
你为什么说你不想见我？
So you misunderstood me.
所以你误会我了。
conscience of heaven and earth
天地良心
How have I wanted to apologize to you these past few days?
这几天我怎么想跟你道歉呢？
At first it was waiting for me to get everything ready.
一开始它在等我把一切准备好。
Find another day to lure you here.
找另一天来吸引你来这里。
Come here to propose marriage.
来这里求婚。
But I don't think
但我不认为
You'll find it yourself.
你自己会找到的。
You don't think
你不认为
These rose pattern candles
这些玫瑰图案蜡烛
Until that time, you can make your request.
在那之前，您可以提出您的要求。
wedding dress
婚纱
ring
戒指
Don't miss even one thing.
甚至不要错过一件事。
Of course, the most important thing is
当然，最重要的是
Must organize a magnificent wedding as well.
还必须举办一场盛大的婚礼。
Otherwise, I won't promise.
不然我不会答应。
The Chen family made a serious promise.
陈家郑重承诺。
No matter what it is, it probably doesn't matter.
不管它是什么，可能都不重要。
Lao Lu
Lao Lu
I submitted a request to the organization.
我向该组织提交了请求。
allow me to marry Zuo Shuangtao
allow me to marry Zuo Shuangtao
Have you thought this through?
你考虑清楚了吗？
It's not wrong.
这并没有错。
Point one
第一点
If I refuse marriage
如果我拒绝结婚
You will have to meet with people who are suspicious.
你必须会见可疑的人。
Hidden work from now on
从现在开始隐藏工作
I can't escape it either.
我也无法逃避。
Secondly
第二
Previously, I left without saying goodbye.
之前，我不辞而别。
Wrong with Zuo Shuangtao
Wrong with Zuo Shuangtao
I want her family
我想要她的家人
From the bottom of my heart I want happiness for you.
我从心底里希望你幸福。
The first point you make I agree with.
你提出的第一点我同意。
As for the second story
至于第二个故事
Zuo Shuangtao is not our person.
左双涛不是我们的人。
marry her
娶她
must pass strict inspections
必须经过严格的检查
I know that Lao Lu
我知道老鲁
But one year ago, Zuo Shuangtao
But one year ago, Zuo Shuangtao
and my marriage application
和我的结婚申请
It has been approved.
已获批准。
Anyway, 1 year ago
无论如何，1年前
Now the situation has changed.
现在情况发生了变化。
You have a hidden mission.
你有一个隐藏的任务。
When are you husband and wife?
你们什么时候成为夫妻了？
We meet in the morning and in the evening, we can rely on each other.
我们朝夕相见，可以互相依靠。
With a close relationship like this
有了这样亲密的关系
How can you guarantee your own safety?
怎样才能保证自己的安全呢？
My elders promised.
我的长辈答应了。
I will protect my identity as best I can.
我将尽我所能保护我的身份。
If I don't have a way
如果我没有办法
I would never say this opinion to you.
我永远不会对你说这个意见。
And what about Zuo Shuang Tao?
那么左双涛呢？
Who are you?
你是谁？
Do you understand him more fully?
你对他有更全面的了解吗？
Your ideas have always been progressive.
你的想法一直都是进步的。
How can you guarantee it for more than 1 year?
怎么能保证1年以上呢？
Your thoughts haven't changed at all.
你的想法根本没有改变。